<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Leather_WoWNightElf.label>暗夜精灵皮</Leather_WoWNightElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWNightElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Night Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWNightElf.description>

  <Leather_WoWBloodElf.label>血精灵皮</Leather_WoWBloodElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWBloodElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Blood Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWBloodElf.description>

  <Leather_WoWHighElf.label>高等精灵皮</Leather_WoWHighElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWHighElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped High Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWHighElf.description>

  <Leather_WoWForsaken.label>被遗忘者皮</Leather_WoWForsaken.label>
  <Leather_WoWForsaken.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Tau skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWForsaken.description>

  <Leather_WoWOrc.label>兽人皮</Leather_WoWOrc.label>
  <Leather_WoWOrc.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Tau skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWOrc.description>

  <Leather_WoWTroll.label>巨魔皮</Leather_WoWTroll.label>
  <Leather_WoWTroll.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Tau skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWTroll.description>

  <Leather_WoWMagharOrc.label>玛格汉兽人皮</Leather_WoWMagharOrc.label>
  <Leather_WoWMagharOrc.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Mag'har Orc skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWMagharOrc.description>

  <Leather_WoWNightborne.label>夜之子皮</Leather_WoWNightborne.label>
  <Leather_WoWNightborne.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Nightborne skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWNightborne.description>

  <Leather_WoWVoidElf.label>虚空精灵皮</Leather_WoWVoidElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWVoidElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Void Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWVoidElf.description>

</LanguageData>