<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- BloodElf Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWBloodElf.label>血精灵皮</Leather_WoWBloodElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWBloodElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Blood Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWBloodElf.description>


  <!-- Draenei Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWDraenei.label>draenei leather</Leather_WoWDraenei.label>
  <Leather_WoWDraenei.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Blood Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWDraenei.description>


  <!-- Dwarf Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWDwarf.label>dwarf leather</Leather_WoWDwarf.label>
  <Leather_WoWDwarf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped dwarf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWDwarf.description>


  <!-- Forsaken Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWForsaken.label>被遗忘者皮</Leather_WoWForsaken.label>
  <Leather_WoWForsaken.description>Rotting, dried, scraped, Forsaken skin. Most people find this material utterly disgusting and horrifying. This leather being rotted, neither protects nor insulates particularly well. Smells pretty bad too.</Leather_WoWForsaken.description>


  <!-- Gnome Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWGnome.label>gnome leather</Leather_WoWGnome.label>
  <Leather_WoWGnome.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Gnome skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWGnome.description>


  <!-- Goblin Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWGoblin.label>goblin leather</Leather_WoWGoblin.label>
  <Leather_WoWGoblin.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Goblin skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWGoblin.description>


  <!-- HighElf Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWHighElf.label>高等精灵皮</Leather_WoWHighElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWHighElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped High Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWHighElf.description>


  <!-- NightElf Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWNightElf.label>暗夜精灵皮</Leather_WoWNightElf.label>
  <Leather_WoWNightElf.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Night Elf skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWNightElf.description>


  <!-- Orc Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWOrc.label>兽人皮</Leather_WoWOrc.label>
  <Leather_WoWOrc.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Tau skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWOrc.description>


  <!-- Tauren Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWTauren.label>tauren leather</Leather_WoWTauren.label>
  <Leather_WoWTauren.description>The furry pelt of a tauren. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. Good at temperature regulation in cold climates.</Leather_WoWTauren.description>


  <!-- Troll Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWTroll.label>巨魔皮</Leather_WoWTroll.label>
  <Leather_WoWTroll.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Tau skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWTroll.description>


  <!-- Worgen Leather -->

  <Leather_WoWWorgen.label>worgen leather</Leather_WoWWorgen.label>
  <Leather_WoWWorgen.description>Tanned, dried, scraped Tau skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWWorgen.description>


</LanguageData>