<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Leather_WoWDirewolf.label>dire wolf leather</Leather_WoWDirewolf.label>
  <Leather_WoWDirewolf.description>The strong furry leather of a dire wolf. Compared to most leather, it is quite a bit tougher and a bit better at all kinds of temperature regulation.</Leather_WoWDirewolf.description>

  <Leather_WoWRaptor.label>raptor leather</Leather_WoWRaptor.label>
  <Leather_WoWRaptor.description>The tanned skin of a cold-blooded reptile. Raptorskin is reasonably tough, but does not insulate well at all.</Leather_WoWRaptor.description>

  <Leather_WoWHorse.label>horse leather</Leather_WoWHorse.label>
  <Leather_WoWHorse.description>Tanned, dried, scraped horse skin. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWHorse.description>

  <Leather_WoWUnicorn.label>unicorn leather</Leather_WoWUnicorn.label>
  <Leather_WoWUnicorn.description>Tanned, dried, scraped unicorn skin. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWUnicorn.description>

  <Leather_WoWForsakenhorse.label>forsaken horse leather</Leather_WoWForsakenhorse.label>
  <Leather_WoWForsakenhorse.description>Tanned, dried, scraped forsaken horse skin. Most people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_WoWForsakenhorse.description>

  <Leather_WoWNightsaber.label>nightsaber leather</Leather_WoWNightsaber.label>
  <Leather_WoWNightsaber.description>A soft furry pelt harvested from a nightsaber. It is difficult to pierce and insulates well against heat.</Leather_WoWNightsaber.description>

  <Leather_WoWHawkstrider.label>hawkstrider leather</Leather_WoWHawkstrider.label>
  <Leather_WoWHawkstrider.description>Tanned, dried, scraped hawkstrider skin. It is quite delicate. Without its feathers, it provides little protection from heat or cold.</Leather_WoWHawkstrider.description>

  <Leather_WoWKodo.label>kodo leather</Leather_WoWKodo.label>
  <Leather_WoWKodo.description>The tanned skin of a cold-blooded reptile. Kodo-skin is reasonably tough, but does not insulate well at all.</Leather_WoWKodo.description>

  <Leather_WoWDragonhawk.label>dragonhawk leather</Leather_WoWDragonhawk.label>
  <Leather_WoWDragonhawk.description>The tanned skin of a cold-blooded reptile. Dragonhawk-skin is reasonably tough, but does not insulate well at all.</Leather_WoWDragonhawk.description>

  <Leather_WoWMurloc.label>murloc leather</Leather_WoWMurloc.label>
  <Leather_WoWMurloc.description>The tanned skin of a amphibious creature. Murloc-skin isn't very tough, but insulates quite well.</Leather_WoWMurloc.description>

  <Leather_WoWRam.label>ram leather</Leather_WoWRam.label>
  <Leather_WoWRam.description>A soft furry pelt harvested from a ram. It is difficult to pierce and insulates well against heat.</Leather_WoWRam.description>

  <Leather_WoWFairyDragon.label>fairy dragon leather</Leather_WoWFairyDragon.label>
  <Leather_WoWFairyDragon.description>The tanned skin of a cold-blooded reptile. Fairy dragon skin is reasonably tough, but does not insulate well at all.</Leather_WoWFairyDragon.description>


</LanguageData>