<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Child backstories -->

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_1.title>fire-scarred child</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_1.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_1.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was scarred by the fires that burned down Teldrassil which destroyed both [PAWN_pronoun] home and [PAWN_pronoun] family. In the recovery after [PAWN_possessive] helped with the reconstruction of homes but as a result of the traumatic incident they became a social recluse.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_1.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_2.title>novice priestess</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_2.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_2.baseDescription>During [PAWN_possessive] younger days, [PAWN_nameDef] always looked up to the Sisterhood of Elune and dreamed of becoming a priestess. One day [PAWN_nameDef] was scouted by the Sisterhood and upon seeing [PAWN_possessive] talent in both magic and her attunement with nature they decided to accept [PAWN_nameDef] to their ranks.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_2.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_3.title>novice druid</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_3.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_3.baseDescription></WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_3.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_4.title>prodigy</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_4.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_4.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as a child to a pair of sentinels and thus was exposed to art of the bow at a young age. [PAWN_pronoun] became adept with both the glaive and the bow at an astonishing rate, and may soon become a force for the Horde to be reckoned with.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_4.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_5.title>jungle child</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_5.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_5.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was at the Feathermoon Stronghold when the cataclysm caused his homeland to be destroyed along with everything he held dear. [PAWN_pronoun] then survived on [PAWN_possessive] own within the jungle of Feralas foraging for [PAWN_possessive] own food, and fighting for [PAWN_possessive] own survival.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Child_5.baseDescription>


  <!-- Adult backstories -->

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_1.title>watcher</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_1.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_1.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is a jailer and marshal of night elf society. They guard the barrow-prisons of the night elves and hunt down dangerous criminals.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_1.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_2.title>warrior</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_2.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_2.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] has learned to be attune with nature and wield feral power able to charge with the ferocity of a bear, or were trained to protect Teldrassil and other Night Elven lands, whatever the case. You bear a great strength and skill for combat and use this to your advantage, you might be viewed as a hero by many, if you dedicate your sheer skill to protect your people.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_2.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_3.title>traditionalist</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_3.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_3.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] 's parents were born shortly after the beginning of the Long Vigil and they clung tightly to traditional Kaldorei beliefs, especially isolationism. As a result while being one who is attuned with nature and the essence of what it is to be a night elf, they look down upon change and even those different from them.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_3.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_4.title>beast master</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_4.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_4.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] spent their life being surrounded by and raising large beasts such as nightsabers and hippogryphs. In battle the synergy between [PAWN_nameDef]and their animal companions is unparalleled. However with spending so much time with their beloved creatures, it has resulted in a strained relationship with that of their kin.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_4.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_5.title>architect</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_5.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_5.baseDescription>As [PAWN_pronoun] came of age, [PAWN_nameDef] became intrigued by elven architecture and in particular the construction of glaive throwers. While many among [PAWN_pronoun] kin were uninterested in the war machines, [PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated by these siege weapons and spent [PAWN_pronoun] life perfecting [PAWN_pronoun] craft.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_5.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_6.title>adventurer</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_6.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_6.baseDescription>Rather than stay at [PAWN_pronoun] home in Ashenvale, [PAWN_nameDef] decided to venture to the eastern kingdoms in search of excitement and thrill. Through [PAWN_pronoun] 's travels they gained a vast collection of knowledge and fought many new foes.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_6.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_7.title>mooncloth tailor</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_7.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_7.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is one of the few among the Kaldorei adept enough with moonwells to create fine mooncloth, a specialty of the night elves. [PAWN_nameDef]'s hands weave at a speed incomparable to normal craftsmen and could put an average tailor to shame.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_7.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_8.title>moonberry brewer</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_8.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_8.baseDescription>Upon reaching adulthood [PAWN_nameDef] tried a taste of moonberry juice and upon that moment [PAWN_nameDef] knew [PAWN_pronoun] had found a purpose. [PAWN_nameDef] dedicated their life to fermenting moonberries and trying  to create the perfect moonberry juice concoction. While [PAWN_nameDef]'s level of brewing is impressive, [PAWN_pronoun] has a bad habit of partaking in the product a bit too often.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_8.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_9.title>bowyer</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_9.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_9.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef]spends [PAWN_possessive] time inspecting naturally fallen branches to whittle into various types of bow, determined by the size and quality of the branch. [PAWN_nameDef]only picks the best branches and refuses to snap any from living trees.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_9.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_10.title>skinner</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_10.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_10.baseDescription>The Kaldorei do not believe in keeping livestock for harvest, though do not shy away from making use of animal products. [PAWN_nameDef]actively hunts requested beasts for their hides, selling the meat and curing the leather for armour crafters to make use of.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_10.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_11.title>alchemist</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_11.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_11.baseDescription>Most night elves, and anyone other than druids and curious adventurers for that matter, tend to steer clear of Felwood. Not [NAME]. [PAWN_nameDef]is fascinated by the fel corruption's effects on the local flora and has taken to experimenting with it in [PAWN_possessive] potion making. Just to see what happens.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_11.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_12.title>botanist</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_12.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_12.baseDescription>Moonglade is a sacred grove maintained by the druids of the Emerald Circle. [PAWN_nameDef]is one of few permitted to tend to and harvest the herbs that grow there for non-druidic uses.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_12.baseDescription>

  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_13.title>night warrior</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_13.title>
  <WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_13.baseDescription>The Night Warrior, the embodiment of Elune’s wrath. The rite to allow a Kaldorei to become the avatar of the Night Warrior is exceedingly dangerous, almost killing [PAWN_pronoun] in the process of doing so. However the rewards were great, as [PAWN_nameDef] is near unmatched in battle.</WoW_NightElf_Backstory_Adult_13.baseDescription>


</LanguageData>